{
    "subject": "resource/Vesta_M._Roy",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Kenmore,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "Vesta M. Roy died in Kenmore, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9420314431190491,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in Kenmore, New York at the time of Vesta M. Roy's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.902433454990387,
            "question": "Where did Vesta M. Roy die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8324222564697266,
            "question": "What year did Vesta M. Roy die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.783317506313324,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Vesta M. Roy died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5234201550483704,
            "question": "In which state did Vesta M. Roy pass away?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4525989294052124,
            "question": "Was Vesta M. Roy known for anything specific?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4325339198112488,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Vesta M. Roy's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42819616198539734,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Kenmore, New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34233787655830383,
            "question": "Are there any historical records related to Vesta M. Roy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28641530871391296,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Vesta M. Roy's family or friends?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Vesta M. Roy died in Kenmore, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3279_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any historical records related to Vesta M. Roy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3279_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Kenmore, New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3279_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have any information about Vesta M. Roy's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3279_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3279_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple because all of them mention that Vesta M. Roy died in Kenmore, New York. This is mentioned in document 6.txt as follows:\n\n\"Vesta M. Roy (n\u00e9e Coward; March 26, 1925 \u2013 February 9, 2002) was a Republican New Hampshire politician... She died on February 9, 2002, in her Kenmore home after suffering a heart attack.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Vesta M. Roy died in Kenmore, NY, which matches the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}